England
Marist Archives and Special Collections
England
2.1.1.2.4
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1322
- England, 2.1.1.2.4
  - Girl driving Australian soldiers, London, circa 1918; 9; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Australian soldier with arm around girl, sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 10; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Girl with arm around Australian soldier, American soldier in one corner, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 11; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Australian soldier holding child, sitting on bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 12; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Canadian soldier with arm around girl, surrounded by children, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 13; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Soldiers and women sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 14; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Soldiers sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 15; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Soldiers sitting on Balustrade, others standing Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 16; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Sailors and girls sitting on bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 17; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Women standing in front of a statue of a lion near Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 18; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two women standing in front of a statue of a lion near Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 19; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two women, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 20; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two women and a soldier sitting on a bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 21; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Woman standing by statue, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 22; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Poster for the women’s land army at the base of Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 23; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Poster for women’s land army at base of Nelson’s Column, drummers in foreground, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 24; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Women standing in rows, circa 1918; 25; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Crowds watching women march down street, circa 1918; 26; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two land army girls, London, circa 1918; 27; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - American soldier (“Doughboy””) talking to land army girls, London, circa 1918; 28; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Four wagons filled with soldiers, circa 1918; 29; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Wagons filled with soldiers, circa 1918; 30; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Soldier standing in front of wagon, circa 1918; 31; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Demonstration for State Aid for the Blind, Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 32; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Demonstration for State Aid for the Blind, three soldiers and woman and foreground, Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 33; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Four girls standing in front of a white craft airplane model, London, circa 1918; 34; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - American soldier and London horse Guard, circa 1918; 35; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - American soldier, sailor and London horse Guard, circa 1918; 36; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Three soldiers and woman, with dog, in front of tents, London, circa 1918; 37; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - British soldiers sewing socks, London, circa 1918; 38; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Soldiers leaving a Y.M.C.A, circa 1918; 39; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Group of soldiers and sailors, American Y.M.C.A in background, London, circa 1918; 40; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, poster for American Y.M.C.A. in foreground, circa 1918; 41; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, Canadian Y.M.C.A., Hotel Cecil in background, London, circa 1918; 42; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, double-decker buses, Morley’s Hotel, London, circa 1918; 43; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Street scene, double-decker bus, Morley’s Hotel, London, circa 1918; 44; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Charing Cross Hotel, circa 1918; 45; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two men on horses, Victorian Hotel in background, circa 1918; 46; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Whitehead and his two children in garden, London, circa 1918; 47; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Whitehead’s home, house and lawn, circa 1918; 48; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Whitehead’s home, lawn and waterfront, London, circa 1918; 49; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Whitehead’s home, lawn, two people in distance, London, circa 1918; 50; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Washington Inn, soldier on bench in foreground, statue in distance, London, circa 1918; 51; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Washington Inn, soldiers in foreground, London, circa 1918; 52; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Balloon automobile in front of the Oceanic House, London, circa 1918; 53; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Westminster Abbey, London, circa 1918; 54; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Westminster Hospital, Big Ben in distance, London, circa 1918; 55; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Wellington Arch, soldier in foreground, London, circa 1918; 56; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Large statue with lions at base, circa 1918; 57; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Woman standing by lamppost, buildings in distance, London, circa 1918; 58; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Two men standing near ornate fence, large building in distance, London, circa 1918; 59; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Crowd of people in park, circa 1918; 60; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1322)
  - Four military men talking next to man holding advertisement for baseball game, circa 1918; 61; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Three military men walking away from building, circa 1918; 62; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Two military men talking next to Sphinx replica, London, circa 1918; 63; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Two women wearing “Royal Flying Corps” uniforms on motorcycle and sidecar, circa 1918; 64; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  - Three people sitting on bench in front of fountain, circa 1918; 65; 4x5 (Box 1322)
  Box 1323
- England, 2.1.1.2.4
  - Crowd of people, in park, gathered around flagpole, circa 1918; 1; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Crowd of people in park, circa 1918; 2; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Chelsea Football Club, spectators watching game, circa 1918; 3; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Chelsea Football Club, cricket match, circa 1918; 4; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Chelsea Football Club, cricket match, circa 1918; 5; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Crowd sitting near the church army, Lord Kitchener Hut, circa 1918; 6; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Crowd near the church army, Lord Kitchener Hut, circa 1918; 7; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Couple sitting in field, crowd in background, circa 1918; 8; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Canadian soldier, woman and child sitting in field, crowd in background, circa 1918; 9; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Little boy, saluting, wearing H.M.S. diadem hat, circa 1918; 10; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - Little girl wearing hat from the H.M.S. Queen Mary, circa 1918; 11; 5x7 (Box 1323)
  - English submarine, circa 1918; 12; 3.5x5.5 (Box 1323)
  - English submarine, circa 1918; 13; 3.5x5.5 (Box 1323)
  - Man with binoculars, circa 1918; 14; 3.5x5.5 (Box 1323)
  - English submarine, man using binoculars, circa 1918; 15; 3.5x5.5 (Box 1323)
  - Officer of an English submarine, circa 1918; 16; 3.25x4.25 (Box 1323)
  - Officers of English submarines, circa 1918; 17; 3.25x4.25 (Box 1323)
  - Crew and officers, English submarine, circa 1918; 18; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)
  - Person wearing long coat, British Submarine, circa 1918; 19; 3.5x4.5 (Box 1323)